

#### **Mohammad Salman**

UI Developer at Mantra Group

Hyderabad, Telangana, India salmanuidev1407@gmail.com | 9618379105



## **About**

I have around 4+ years of work experience in UI Developer at Mantra. I have worked on my relevant technical skills like e.g: HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3, Bootstrap, Vue Bootstrap, SASS, Tailwind CSS, Tailwind UI, JavaScript, Vue js.

Graduate from Aurora Scientific and Technical Institute of Engineering.

#### Top Skills

- HTML/HTML5
- CSS/CSS3 • Bootstrap, Vue Bootstrap
- SASS, Tailwind CSS, Tailwind UI
- JavaScript, Vue.js.

My proficiency extends to the entire software development life cycle (SDLC), enabling me to design and develop captivating user experiences for web applications.

#### **Experience**



## Mantra

4 yrs 10 mos

#### Senior UI Developer

Jun 2022 - Present. 1 yr 5 mos Hyderabad, Telangana, India

**Skills:** HTML/HTML5 · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) · CSS3 · CSS Grid Layout · Mobile Device Responsive

· Responsive Web Design · CSS Flexbox · Bootstrap · Vue bootstrap · Tailwind UI · Tailwind CSS · JavaScript · Vue.js · GitHub

#### UI Developer

May 2019 - Jun 2022. 3 yrs 2 mos

Hyderabad Area, India

**Skills:** Git · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) · HTML5 · Css3 · BootstrapVue · Bootstrap4 · SASS · JavaScript · Vue.js · GitHub

· Responsive Web Design · Mobile Responsive

#### UI Developer Trainee

Jan 2019 - Apr 2019. 3 mos

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

**Skills:** HTML · CSS Sprites · CSS Flexbox · Bootstrap · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS).

#### **Education**



#### **Aurora Scientific and Technology Institute**

B. Tech, Computer Science 2012 - 2016

#### **Projects**

#### **GharPe - Direct From Builders**

Oct 2022 - Present

#### **Description:**

With our virtual platform, you can connect with sellers, take video tours of properties, and mark your visits as done – all without leaving your home. India's first platform to see your properties in 3D View, Drone View. Development Environment: HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind UI, Tailwind CSS, Responsive Design.

## **Roles and Responsibilities:**

Developed Responsive webpages using HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind UI, Tailwind CSS, and Vuejs. Performed Functional Manipulations (on click events, hide/show events, data binding using handlebars, etc.). Performed Functional Public pages using Tailwind UI and Vuejs Framework by fetching data and data binding through FastAPI. Make a few components like Scheduling a Tour, Media, etc. UI/UX Design issues for Enhancements and Bugs Fixes. Involved in Code Review sessions by Development Team.

**Skills:** · HTML5 · Tailwind UI · Tailwind CSS · CSS Grid Layout · Mobile Device Responsive · CSS Flexbox · CSS3 · JavaScript · Vue Site link - <a href="https://gharpe.com">https://gharpe.com</a>

#### Apr 2021 - Dec 2021

**Projectsly - Project Management Software** 

**Description:** 

This is a project management tool it can perform as to plan office works well, track it effectively, and collaborate with team members efficiently like never before. Here we can streamline office project planning. Plan every aspect of a project from start to finish to accelerate business growth. Smart team collaboration and communicate with team in real-time to keep projects on track.

# **Roles and Responsibilities:**

Developed Responsive webpages using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap Vue and SASS. Performed Basic Vue Js Manipulations (on click events, hide/show events etc.). UI/UX Design issues for Enhancements and Bugs Fixes. Involved in Code Review sessions by Development Team.

**Skills:** CSS Grid Layout · Mobile Device Responsive · CSS Flexbox · CSS3 · HTML5 · BootstrapVue · Bootstrap4 · JavaScript · Vue.js · Mobile Responsive Site link - <a href="https://projectsly.com">https://projectsly.com</a>

### Dec 2020 - Oct 2021

Support.cc - Help Desk Support Software

**Description:** 

### Delight your customers with multi-channel Help Desk Software - email ticketing, social responses, phone calls, task

management, smart bots is a simple start **Roles and Responsibilities:** 

Developed Responsive webpages using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap Vue and SASS. Performed Basic Vue Js Manipulations (on click events, hide/show events etc.). UI/UX Design issues for Enhancements and Bugs Fixes. Involved in Code Review sessions

by Development Team. **Skills:** CSS Grid Layout · Mobile Device Responsive · CSS Flexbox · CSS3 · HTML5 · BootstrapVue · Bootstrap4 · JavaScript · Vue.js · Mobile Responsive

Site link - <a href="https://support.cc">https://support.cc</a>

"Involved in Multiple Products like Finder.io, CRM.io and Pushly Etc.

